I don't like the war. You've worked with
directly with President Trump. And if
you read their constitution, uh the
first couple of sentences is they want
to
foment and they want to project the
Iranian radical Islamic
cult.
I'm also observing 25 years of history
of the Americans in the Middle East
trying to create regime change uh with
no success. So, we replaced the Taliban
with the Taliban.
President says that the country pays the
tariff. That does not who pays the
tariff. American people pay the tariff.
Oh, now hopefully I'm wrong. But,
hopefully tonight we'll wake [music] up
and it's a V-shaped uh bounce.
Well, when you're 15, 16, 17 and you're
reading the paper about current events
and it's the president of this country,
the prime minister of that country,
you're thinking that they put their
pants on differently than you. You know,
you think you're thinking they're
special and because
>> [music]
>> of what your financial means are and
where you're living, you think you're
not. One of the big realizations for me
in my life is that uh your opportunity
comes a lot from frankly your
upbringing, a lot from your brain
chemistry, and a lot from your belief
system. You could play with anybody.
Fight is on the inside. Remember Henry
Ford once said something Bonnie, so
listen very carefully. If you think you
can
or you think you can't, you're right.
>> [music]
[music]
>> My guest today, Anthony Scaramucci, he's
one of my favorite, founder of SkyBridge
Capital, Trumena Salt. He also served as
the White House Communications Director
during Trump's first term. And here's
his bestseller, The Little Book of
Bitcoin has just been translated into
Chinese.
Um what a fantastic book. Hello Anthony.
Well, first of all, thank you. And I
want to stay your favorite, okay? So, I
got to get out of this interview with
you still liking me, Bonnie, right?
That's my goal.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. Okay. Well, okay, first question I
have to ask you about uh the war. No,
listen, I don't like the war. I wouldn't
have done the war. I don't recommend the
war. The war always leads to
a doctrine of unintended consequences.
And if you even just think about what is
the best
outcome for the United States or for the
Gulf countries,
uh it's still a very murky outcome. So,
you know, you're you're better off not
having wars, frankly. That's just my
personal opinion. We're in it now.
Um I don't see a 93 million person
country with a 5,000-year history
uh just giving up right away. I just
don't see that happening. And um
you know, we don't do regime change well
in the United States. So, we have a very
bad track record. We replaced the
Taliban with the Taliban uh after 20
years of fighting. And so, for me, I'm I
don't like it. And I wish I wish they
didn't do it. But we're in it now. I'm
an American. I I wish our troops great
safety and success.
But uh I can't believe, and I go to the
Gulf a lot, as you probably know. I'm in
Abu Dhabi all the time, Dubai,
Bahrain, I'm in Qatar. I can't believe
that the Gulf states are happy about
this. Just can't believe that they would
be, because it's just it's hurting the
real estate prices, it's hurting
everything. Now,
>> Are they happy about it?
I don't think that they are, no. I don't
think they are. So, people are saying
that they the Gulf states wanted this. I
don't think so. That open letter from
the uh Dubai billionaire, uh I don't
know him well. I've met him once.
Uh I don't think MBZ would have ever let
that letter go out if uh
you know, he didn't sanction the letter.
So, I don't think they're happy about
it. Look, it is
it is what it is. We'll see what
happens. What's interesting though is,
as you've seen, Bitcoin has a bid.
Bitcoin hasn't really gone through
its say interest cycle low of 60,000.
Um and looking at it today, the price is
relatively firm given everything that we
know about oil prices and other assets.
So,
I feel like Bitcoin is this sneaky
instrument, Bonnie. It It led us into
this thing, you know, when everything
seemed superficially okay, Bitcoin
crashed 40%.
And now that everything is not okay, and
it's more than just superficial, Bitcoin
it seems to be fairly stable. 15% of
Iranians support this current regime,
very low. So, many people
want this change, but they're probably
scared. Um there's this speech that
Trump said, you know, the hour of
freedom is at your hand. Now is the time
to seize control of your destiny.
I say tonight that the hour of your
freedom is at hand. Now is the time to
seize control of your destiny and to
unleash the prosperous and glorious
future. But, what do you think would
happen realistically?
Well, you have to understand something
that there's 47 years of suppression.
You know, I can't imagine after 4 years
of war in Russia that the Russian
population is super supportive of that
war, but you have a police state and you
have a, you know, you have a security
system around the country that's
repressing the people. So, so I I accept
that, but I say those people are
generally unarmed. Uh those people can
go into a protest in the street um by
anybody's count. You have to tell me
there's a lot of disinformation. The
Iranians say 3,000 people were killed
there in the January protest. The
Americans are saying it's 30,000. Uh I'm
not sure which number is correct, but
that's 3,000 or 30,000 too many. So, um
you have to be very realistic about
these things. I want there to be peace.
I recognize the repression of the
regime. I'm not sitting here as an
apologist for Iran. Of course, it's a
repressive regime and it's something
that I would like to have end. It's been
47 years of uh heartbreak for the
Americans in the West as it relates to
that country. I will also point out to
people listening to your show that if
you read their constitution,
uh the first couple of sentences is they
want to
foment and they want to project
the Iranian radical
Islamic
cult, if you will, or however you want
to describe it, you know, the Islamic
Republic of Iran, they want to export it
to other places. They've been a state
sponsor of terrorism.
They have Iranian militias in Iraq that
have wreaked havoc. Obviously, they have
funded Hamas and Hezbollah with their
oil proceeds, which has put a hurt on
Israel, which is one of our strongest
allies. So, so I'm I'm a very realistic
person about who they are and what they
are,
but I'm also observing 25 years of
history of the Americans in the Middle
East trying to create regime change uh
with no success. And so, we probably
spent 8 to 10 trillion dollars, millions
of people have died, tens of thousands
of Americans wounded and or killed. And
so, I it it's hard for me to understand
after that experience over the last 25
years,
why we're going in this direction, you
know. I'm just saying to you as a
rationalist and a pragmatist,
um there were other ways to go about
this. I think I think we're going to
find, frankly,
that in the uh
situation in Oman, there was a deal on
the table and we're going to have to
understand more carefully why that deal
wasn't accepted. I mean, even taking our
uh ready you know, uranium enrichment
down to near zero for the country. There
was a negotiation about 3 weeks ago in
Oman where the Americans were there with
the Iranians and then the talks
apparently broke down, but um
you know, the Iranians agreed to the
terms that the Americans wanted.
Okay, so the question is why did why did
we why do we not take those terms? We we
We said, "Okay, here's the terms." And
the Iranians said, "Okay, we're going to
give you those terms." And then we
didn't take them. So,
so listen, um
Listen, I'm not a pacifist either. I get
the fact that sometimes you have to use
the military and you have to, you know,
you have to protect our interests around
the world. I'm I I understand all of
that. But I just think this is a really
bad situation and and when you're
learning that the Russians are providing
signal intelligence uh to help target
Iranian missiles and the president is, I
guess, okay with that and the
president's going to help
I guess Vladimir Putin in Ukraine. I
don't know. It doesn't It doesn't
It's not add It doesn't doesn't add up
to me, you know? So, but again, I'm an
American. I want to I want to support
our troops and I obviously am praying
for a great outcome, but
but uh you know, as it relates to
Bitcoin
I think other assets are going to fall a
lot. I think Bitcoin is already had its
uh crash. It's I think we've hit our
intra-cycle low. That's just me
personally. I think it's the I think
it's that $60,000 number. It feels
pretty sturdy here in the mid-60s.
And um everybody's got different
opinions of Bitcoin. I'm more in the uh
4-year cycle of Bitcoin. And I really
feel like you won't see Bitcoin rallying
until the end of this year. Probably be
starting in the fourth quarter
uh just because of the way the uh
economics are around the mining, the
hash rate, uh the having cycle uh
coming. You know, we're 2 years into the
uh the last having. As you get towards
the third year, you'll start to see more
robust activity in Bitcoin. So,
I even though we have institutions in
there and all this other stuff, I still
see the traditional 4-year cycle for the
asset.
What about other assets? You know,
for example, last year liberation day,
it was a V-shape recovery. Are we going
to see that now in in case the market
crash
a little more?
>> [sighs]
>> Well, I mean again, you know, you you
you have to tell me what's going to
happen if you just tell me the Americans
say, "Okay, I get you. Trump is prone to
do anything." You can say, "We've we've
won." Whether we've won or we haven't
and he pulls back our offensive
operation, will that stop the Iranians
from bombing our Gulf allies? You know,
presumably it would and maybe that would
cause a V-shape, but I
I think a lot of damage has been done
because you know, you've taken out a few
of our uh
uh
satellite imagery radar systems.
Um that's factual. Both the Americans
and the Iranians are saying that. Um the
Gulf states have felt generally
unprotected. Uh we put bases in a lot of
those areas and they have felt generally
unprotected. I think you've upset the
apple cart. I think you've upset the
balance of what's going on in the Middle
East. So so even if you get
you know, I don't know what's the
outcome. You know you know the the the
the Trump administration stands down or
something like that. You tell me. I mean
I I don't see how you get to a regime
change without boots on the ground.
Moreover, put the boots on the ground.
Look at what happened in Iraq. You had
10 years of resistance, 10 years of
ISIS.
You know, look it's not clear to me that
that's going to be the answer. So so I'm
sitting here
looking at various outcomes.
Um the American outcomes are very
different from the Israeli outcomes. You
know, the Israelis you know, Trump was
looking to negotiate with somebody.
He was looking for a Delcy Rodriguez.
Delcy of course is now the president of
Venezuela. She was the number two from
Maduro. Trump basically went to her and
tried to cut a deal. So he was looking
to do that, but the Israelis killed 40
or 50 people, some of which were
secularists.
So you know, we have diverging interests
with the Israelis. And again,
I try to understand the Israelis.
They've been terrorized by Iran
for 40 plus years. This attack on
October 7th obviously really
hurt the country, hit the country. The
situation in Gaza is an unspeakable
tragedy. And whatever side of it you're
on, I think we can stipulate that it's a
tragedy on both sides. So so to me
I I I don't see the way out of this
cleanly.
Now hopefully I'm wrong. Hopefully
tonight we'll wake up and it's a
V-shaped bounce like the liberation day.
But again,
you you you talk about a liberation day
October April 2nd, it was an unforced
error by the United States. There was no
reason going do that. Moreover, the
Supreme Court ruled that what the
president was doing was illegal.
So So, he did something illegal. We all
looked at it and said, "Okay, you can't
do that." Did it anyway. We took in the
tariff revenues, which is an unlegal
illegal tax. I just want to point out to
everybody when the president says that
the country pays the tariff, that does
not who pays the tariff. American people
pay the tariff.
And so, this sort of stuff is uh
to me
um poor management. You know, when you
have good executive management uh really
good things happen. You know, I was in
Belfast last week. I had a live show
with Alister Campbell, the former uh
uh aide to Tony Blair. Uh we had 2,000
people at at the convention center in
Belfast. And we were just talking about
good policy, good governmental policy,
better quality of life. Uh there are 30
years now since they signed this uh
treaty or 28 years since they signed
this treaty in Northern Ireland. And
there's a whole group of people growing
up in Northern Ireland in peace.
Uh they don't have the trauma of their
ancestors, of the constant bombing, and
the constant fighting. So So, good
policy you get good outcomes, you get
peace and prosperity. Bad policy where
nobody can tell you what the end game
is, and nobody can suggest to you
uh which way it's going to go. Um that's
that that's dismaying, to say the least,
you know.
Um I think a lot of people are wondering
you've worked with directly with
President Trump. Is this the end of, you
know, America leading the global
stability?
Um or what is happening with Venezuela,
with Iran?
>> I'm a I'm a realist. What What the
Americans are doing
is outside of the ambit of the 80 years
of the rules-based order that they tried
to create. And so now we're acting
unilaterally and frankly we're letting
one person
run things, okay? So we have more or
less revoked the War Powers Act. Uh if
you read the War Powers Act, you have to
have an imminent danger.
The president does have He is the
commander-in-chief. There's an imminent
danger to the United States. You don't
have to go through the Congress. You
have to you know you have to give the
guy some flexibility to act. Is Was Iran
an imminent danger to the United States?
Um our intelligence officials when they
briefed the Senate Intelligence
Committee said no, it wasn't. So you
know so you're stretching all of the
rules even inside the United States and
you're stretching the Constitution for
this one man. So the reason why I have
been critical, we have done better and
the beauty of the blockchain is in its
decentralization. The beauty of the
American government frankly is in its
decentralization.
Uh the fact that there wasn't
centralized power in the United States
to speak of where each branch of
government had separate but equal
authority, it really allowed the country
to flourish. You you weren't going to
get one hegemon. You weren't going to
get one autocrat
uh to stiff the American people. And
when you study autocracies, what
typically happens is the people at the
very top, there's a funnel of corruption
and the people that are close to the
leader, they do very very well. And the
rest of the people feel general
unfairness
about the situation and then they go
from having aspirations
to feeling economically desperate. So So
to me um what he's doing is against the
200 and we're almost 250 years old. It's
against it's against that. But we don't
have a Congress that's willing to fight
and stand up to him. You know there's
nobody standing up to him. So I mean And
and it got By the way, we're moving
through the news cycles very quickly,
Bonnie. So a couple of weeks ago, maybe
eight seven eight weeks ago, we're
talking about the invasion of Greenland.
And so, the notion that we were going to
invade a NATO-based country and take
over their land,
you know, we had the, you know, well,
some of the people in the Congress did
go to him privately and say, "Okay,
well, we'll probably have to figure out
a way to get you out of office if you
want to continue uh talking like that
and and speaking like that." So, now
we're back Now we're in Iran. So, the
president likes attention,
likes making money for himself. He's
made over $4 billion for himself and his
family in the last year.
Um it's just we're we're going against
every norm that the
that's worked. You know, there's an
irony here,
and I'm going to say it to you in a way
that uh
makes me sad, but there's an irony here.
Everything that's worked to make America
prosperous and to help people like me
who grew up with no money and were able
to live the American dream, we're doing
it in reverse now. You just mentioned
about, you know, growing up and all
that. Last time we did the show, it was
with David Lynn, and Yeah.
>> First of all, before I ask you that
question, I really want to thank you
because when we first met in New York
with David Lynn, um that was my first
ever conference, and I told you
>> Davos? Where was that? At the Davos?
>> Exactly. You told me, I don't know if
you remember this, "I got you."
And, you know, the rest is history. I've
been doing this uh ever since. So, thank
you so much. That really made a really
big impact.
>> Look, you got to listen to me.
Everything in life is about m- the f-
it's the fight is on the inside. You
know, you know, I Remember Henry Ford
once said something, Bonnie. You should
listen very carefully. If you think you
can
or you think you can't, you're right.
Okay? Think about that, okay?
>> [clears throat]
>> The fight's on the inside. Okay, you got
it, you know, you're talented, you're
extremely good at what you're
doing, and you have great capabilities.
You have to believe that. Once you
believe that, you're capable of doing
anything.
It's an It's an It's an inside game,
Bonnie. Don't forget that about life.
>> I I I have talked about this in multiple
podcasts, and I love I love you for
that. Thank you. And um from last um
conversation as well, I I asked you
about growing up in, you know, a
blue-collar family and becoming very
successful. And you said, if you could
go back and tell your younger self, you
would tell him to be way more sure of
himself. Is there any like personal
story you could share?
Well, I mean, listen, I
like you and many other people, I was
intimidated and felt insecure
about my role in the world. And so, as
an example, when you're 15, 16, 17, and
you're reading the paper about current
events, and it's the president of this
country, the prime minister of that
country, you're thinking that they put
their pants on differently than you. You
know, you think you're thinking they're
special, and because of what your
financial means are and where you're
living, and you think you're not. Um but
as I said to one of my buddies at
Harvard Law School who was
talking very pedantically to me, I said,
"Let me tell you something, buddy. There
are people putting sheetrock in my
neighborhood. They're installing
sheetrock that are way smarter than you.
Okay, so calm yourself down. Uh they
just had parents that were putting in
sheetrock, and they didn't have your
opportunity. So, so calm down. So, I
think one of the big realizations for me
in my life is that uh your opportunity
comes a lot from, frankly, your
upbringing, a lot from your brain
chemistry, and a lot from your belief
system. So, so uh I can sit here today
at 62 and tell you that, you know, you
can play with anybody. Okay, they give
you the ball, you'll put the ball in the
hoop. Okay, so don't don't let anybody
intimidate you. Don't let anybody think
that they're better than you. Now, the
flip side of that is because I grew up
in a blue-collar neighborhood, I don't
think I'm better than anybody. You know,
so if I'm in a a hotel, my grandmother
was once a maid. I often think, "Hey,
this person cleaning this room could be
somebody's grandmother." So, want to
make sure I leave them a gratuity and
and treat them with kindness and
dignity. So, uh you're no better than
anybody, Bonnie, but you're no worse
than anybody. I think that's the big
messaging uh from my life. And that's
that's basically my realization, you
know.
I love that. Before I let you go, your
son AJ bought a Pokémon card for 16
million dollars.
>> million, yeah.
What What crossed your mind after
learning that?
>> Well, listen, I'm proud. He's an avid
collector. He's a serial entrepreneur.
He's a venture capitalist. He went to
Stanford Business School. Uh he's been a
Pokémon collector his whole life. I
think he sees that as a one-of-one. And
I think he sees it as a unique asset.
And remember, these avid Pokémon
collectors are in their 30s. Imagine
these guys when they're in their 60s.
And I think the possibilities are
endless. Uh but he's also building a
treasure company. He calls it Treasure
Trove. And so, you know, I'm very very
proud of him and I wish him great
success with it. He wants, you know,
he's telling me he wants to buy a T-Rex.
He wants to buy a uh Declaration
[laughter]
of Independence. And so, you know,
before you know it, he'll probably have
a lot of assets
uh on his balance sheet that I think are
irreplaceable.
So, yeah. I mean, listen, uh
that was a big purchase.
But, he also uh we're talking about it,
you and I. A lot of people talk about
it. He He captured the internet with it.
And uh I'm people He's arrived. And so,
I'm very proud of him. For everyone
watching, I'll put the link of
Bit Boy Tom Shue the Little Book of
Bitcoin down below. Get a coffee. It is
super easy to read and one of the best
way to understand Bitcoin if you're just
starting. We're also giving you a few
copy of this book, so tell us in the
comment section what you love most about
this conversation and share it with your
family and friends. Then you'll have a
chance to win this book. Thank you
again, Anthony.